The letters are out.
To All the Boys I've Loved Before is a comedy,
romance film directed by Susan Johnson.
Lara Jean's love life goes from imaginary to out of control when her secret
letters to every boy she's ever fallen for are mysteriously mailed out.
Lara Jean Song Covey, played by Lana Condor.
Peter Kavinsky, played by Noah Centineo.
Josh Sanderson, played by Israel Broussard.
Margot Song Covey, played by Janel Parrish.
Katherine "Kitty" Song Covey, played by Anna Cathcart.
Greg Rivera, played by Andrew Bachelor.
To All the Boys I've Loved Before is a 2018 American teen romantic comedy
film directed by Susan Johnson and written by Sofia Alvarez.
The film stars Lana Condor, Noah Centineo, Janel Parrish, Anna Cathcart,
Madeleine Arthur, Emilija Baranac, Israel Broussard and John Corbett.
The movie is based on Jenny Han's 2014 novel of the same name,
and was released by Netflix on August 17, 2018.
It received positive reviews from critics, who praised the cast.
It has been the first installment in what is now
the To All the Boys film series.
It was followed by two sequels, To All the Boys: P.S.
I Still Love You, released on February 12, 2020, and To All the
Boys: Always and Forever on February 12, 2021.
A spin-off series titled XO, Kitty was released on May 18, 2023.
The film explores themes of high school, based on novel or
book, love letter, romance, first love.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.